LIDAR stands for Light Detection and Ranging, just as RADAR stands for
LIDARは 「光による探知および 測距」の 略語です  RADARは
RAdio Detection And Ranging.
「電波による探知および測距」ですね
Unlike RADAR, which uses radio waves, LIDAR uses an infrared laser
RADARは 電波を 使いますが LIDARは 赤外線レーザー光線を
beam to determine the distance between the sensor and a nearby object.
使って センサーと 近くにある物体との 距離を 特定します
Most current LIDARs use light in the 900 nanometer wavelength range, although
現在の LIDARの 多くは 900ナノメートルの 波長帯の 光線を使いますが
some LIDARs use longer wavelengths, which perform better in rain and fog.
一部の LIDARは より長い波長を 使い 雨や 霧の中で 高い性能を 発揮します
In current LIDARs,
現在の LIDARでは
a rotating swivel scans the laser beam across the field of view.
回転スイベルが 視野全体で レーザー光線を スキャンします
The lasers are pulsed, and the pulses are reflected by objects.
パルスレーザーを 使っていて パルスが 物体に当たって 反射します
These reflections return a point cloud that represents these objects.
この反射光が 物体を表す ポイントクラウドを 戻します
LIDAR has a much higher spatial resolution than RADAR
LIDARは 空間分解能が RADARより ずっと高いのですが
because of the more focused laser beam, the larger number of scan layers in
それは レーザー光線の 集中度が 高いことや 縦方向の スキャン層が多いこと
the vertical direction, and the high density of LIDAR points per layer.
1層あたりの LIDARポイントの 密度が 高いことに 起因します
The current generation of LIDARs cannot measure the velocity of objects
最新世代の LIDARは 物体の速度を 直接 測定することが
directly.
できず
And have to rely on the differing position between two or more scans.
複数のスキャンの間の 位置の差に 頼らなければ なりません
LIDARs are also more affected by weather conditions and
また LIDARは 気象条件や センサーに付いた ほこりの 影響を
by dirt on the sensor, which requires keeping them clean.
受けやすいため 清潔に 保つ必要があります
They are also much bulkier than other sensors and therefore,
他の センサーより ずっと かさばるため
more difficult to integrate unless one just wants to mount a big scanner
内蔵するのが 難しく 車両のルーフに 大きなセンサーを
on the roof of the vehicle.
取り付ける羽目に なります
So how do we apply LIDAR and RADAR?
では LIDARと RADARは どのように適用するのでしょうか
Let me show you.
お見せしましょう